Just popping in to say that I hypothesize that we can sit here all day and talk about Black
power this and Black power that. However, ultimately, until Haiti is free, I believe
that Black folks in the United States will be indoctrinated. We are in a time loop. And
the last time Black folks in the United States said, you know what? We need to get out of
this thing was when the Haitians did the thing first. But Amanda, how is Haiti not free?
They're not free from still paying France. They're not free from Americans using their
resources and owning their land, i.e. George Bush's family and the Clintons, which own land
together in Labadi. They're not free from Israel sending weapons to keep them destabilized.
Right. So all these gangs like where are these weapons coming from? Exactly. They're not free
from the United States continuing to run their agricultural scenario. So they don't have food
sovereignty, even though they absolutely can grow their own food. In Haiti, they have to eat
American rice, even though they make their own rice. And the American rice is toxic. But when
you understand the abolitionist movement, you understand that it was white abolitionists
who were constantly trying to convince and successfully convincing Black Americans that their pathway to
freedom from enslavement was to pray and to go the nonviolent route and to really just put
any faith and trust and to put all faith and trust into someday white folks in the United States
coming to some level of moral suasion. And it wasn't until they saw what went down in Haiti that they
said, you know what? We maybe should stop listening to y'all because they got free. They did it.
History is not meant to simply tell you about the past. It is to teach you about how to be better,
more effective, and efficient in attaining what you wish for the future in the present.
Haiti and the rest of the Caribbean are the Africa of the Western Hemisphere.
She won that for a second.
D.C. and Bottom Wall, you're up next.
I'm outside y'all doing what I can to decolonize minds on my mission-driven book tour for my new book,
What Would the Ancestors Say?
They say books won't change the world. Tell that to every colonizer that burned them.
Come on out, be in community, buy a book, and get it signed.
RSVP at amandaseals.com